Good day!
طاب يومكم!
This is Quartz News Network at 6.
معكم Quartz News Network على السادسة
I'm your host, Single Seal.
انا مضيفكم, Single Seal.
QNN, Quartz News Network, CRSS Internet, CRSSi, CRSS, ROP, DRR, RFM, FedBank, (The) Strudel, Dema, Blurryface, ThinkSeal, WorldWidePixel, Sauce Dude, Panorama (if referring to the Republic of Panorama), Pooja, Amethyst, Pridecraft Studios, GREAT (the full caps bit, but feel free to translate the rest of the acronym), Northern, Northern II Holidays (when talking about the "brand", do translate "Nothing beats a Northern II *holiday*" but keep "Northern II" in english)
QNN, Quartz News Network, CRSS Internet, CRSSi, CRSS, ROP, DRR, RFM, FedBank, (The) Strudel, Dema, Blurryface, ThinkSeal, WorldWidePixel, Sauce Dude, Panorama (if referring to the Republic of Panorama), Pooja, Amethyst, Pridecraft Studios, GREAT (the full caps bit, but feel free to translate the rest of the acronym), Northern, Northern II Holidays (when talking about the "brand", do translate "Nothing beats a Northern II *holiday*" but keep "Northern II" in english)
Our great Prime Minister, WorldWidePixel, has
رئيس وزرائنا العظيم، WorldWidePixel
revealed that The Republic of Panorama is built on the innovative
أوضح أن جمهورية Panorama قائمة على النظام المبدع
System Wheee.
النظام ويييي
System Whee combines the traditional political power system with
النظام ويي يجمع بين النظام السياسي التقليدي
granting every citizen direct power, but
حيث تمنح السلطة المبشارى لكل المواطنين، ولكن
the citizens' actions must be alligned with a few ground rules set by the Prime Minister.
يجب أن تكون تصرفات المواطنين متوافقة مع بعض القواعد الأساسية التي وضعها رئيس الوزراء.
It's clear its the best system there has ever been
من الواضح أنه أفضل نظام على الإطلاق
as Panorama keeps growing economically and geographically as time passes.
حيث تستمر Panorama في النمو اقتصاديًا وجغرافيًا مع مرور الوقت.
We recently talked about the Instant Chatting Platform
تحدثنا مؤخرًا عن منصة الدردشة الفورية
Pridecraft Studios will be building on the CRSS Internet.
التي ستبنيها Pridecraft Studios على CRSS Internet.
We would now like to announce that “An Independent Organisation” at Strudel
نود الآن أن نعلن أن "منظمة مستقلة" في Strudel
is working on a VoIP solution also running on CRSSi
تعمل على حل VoIP يعمل أيضًا على CRSSi
to assist with Pridecraft's goals!
للمساعدة في تحقيق أهداف Pridecraft!
Scientists and astronauts have just discovered the age of our world
اكتشف العلماء ورواد الفضاء للتو عمر عالمنا
It became two years old on July 10th, 2025 !
لقد أصبح عمره عامين في 10 يوليو 2025!
It's hard to imagine the very same studio we're filming in right now was
من الصعب أن نتخيل أن الاستوديو الذي نصور فيه الآن
just a barren desert not so long ago.
لم يكن سوى صحراء قاحلة منذ وقت ليس ببعيد.
This calls for celebration! But, not at this specific moment.
وهذا يدعو للاحتفال! ولكن ليس في هذه اللحظة بالذات.
We'll have more exciting news after today's sponsor!
سيكون لدينا المزيد من الأخبار المثيرة بعد راعي اليوم!
Darling hold my hand!
يا حبيبتي، أمسكي يدي!
Nothing beats a Northern II Holiday!
لا شيء يضاهي عطلة Northern II!
And right now you can save CAD$ 50, per person!
والآن يمكنك توفير 50 دولارًا كنديًا، للشخص الواحد!
That's CAD$ 200 off for a friend group of four!
وهذا يعني خصم 200 دولار كندي لمجموعة من أربعة أصدقاء!
Are you tired of your server not standing out?
هل سئمت من أن خادمك لا يبرز؟
Do you want your server to appear popular, even though it totally isn't?
هل تريد أن يظهر خادمك بمظهر شائع، على الرغم من أنه ليس كذلك على الإطلاق؟
If your answer to both questions is
إذا كانت إجابتك على كلا السؤالين هي
Yes, or no
نعم، أو لا
Then AdvancedServerList is THE plugin for you!
فإن AdvancedServerList هو الــمكوّن الإضافي المناسب لك!
With AdvancedServerList you can make your server stand out with
مع AdvancedServerList، يمكنك جعل خادمك يبرز بـ
your own ✨cool✨ MOTD
MOTD ✨الرائعة✨ الخاصة بك
a Player count that makes your server look as if it was ✨actually important✨
وعدد لاعبين يجعل خادمك يبدو وكأنه ✨مهم حقًا✨
and a Favicon that will make you 🌟super cool!🌟
وFavicon التي ستجعلك 🌟رائعًا للغاية!🌟
Disclaimer: Coolness level is debatable and not scientifically proven. Your server may remain as boring as it was before using the plug-in.
إخلاء مسؤولية: مستوى الروعة قابل للنقاش وغير مثبت علميًا. قد يظل خادمك مملًا كما كان قبل استخدام المكوّن الإضافي.
Don't wait!
لا تنتظر!
Get AdvancedServerList today!!!
احصل على AdvancedServerList اليوم!!!
We're excited to announce the marriage between Blurry and Piguman
نحن متحمسون للإعلان عن زواج Blurry وPiguman
It's happening right now at The Water Church
إنه يحدث الآن في The Water Church
Let's check them out with our exclusive live cameras.
دعنا نتحقق منهم من خلال كاميراتنا الحية الحصرية.
We are here to see the union of two basement dwellers toda- tonight.
نحن هنا لنشهد اتحاد اثنين من سكان القبو اليوم- الليلة.
That being Blurry and Pigu
وهما Blurry و Pigu
The music you just heard will probably be $0.99 on iTunes in six months.
الموسيقى التي سمعتها للتو ستكون على الأرجح $0.99 على iTunes في غضون ستة أشهر.
Anyway, marriage is more than just love
على أي حال، الزواج هو أكثر من مجرد حب
It's a great way to commit Tax Evas-
إنه طريقة رائعة لارتكاب التهرب الضريبي-
Anyway, seeing as I am - somehow - engaged to two people now
على أي حال، بما أنني - بطريقة ما - مخطوب لشخصين الآن
We will deal with that later.
سنتعامل مع ذلك لاحقًا.
I think it's a great time to celebrate the marriage of Pigu and Blurry.
أعتقد أن هذا وقت رائع للاحتفال بزواج Pigu و Blurry.
I think we are pumped up now.
أعتقد أننا متحمسون الآن.
Really getting into the groove of things.
لقد دخلنا حقًا في أجواء الأمور.
You can pratically taste the energy.
يمكنك أن تتذوق الطاقة عمليًا.
And I've licked these floors more than you wish to know.
ولقد لعقت هذه الأرضيات أكثر مما ترغبون في معرفته.
What?
ماذا؟
Moving on...
ننتقل إلى...
ROP is working on a new Public Transport Network
تعمل ROP على شبكة نقل عام جديدة
This is related to weddings because Blurry worked on it once.
وهذا مرتبط بالأعراس لأن Blurry عمل عليه ذات مرة.
We are fixing the metro!
نحن نصلح المترو!
Anyway, seeing as our couple-to-be is dragging their stylish heels
على أي حال، بما أن عروسينا المنتظرين يتماطلان
We might as well all introduce ourselves.
قد نُعرف أنفسنا جميعًا.
Let's start with ThinkSeal, because they're slacking.
لنبدأ بـ ThinkSeal، لأنهم يتماهلون.
Hi.
مرحبًا.
I am now awake.
أنا مستيقظ الآن.
I code stuff sometimes.
أقوم بترميز الأشياء أحيانًا.
Next is BaLLducked
التالي هو BaLLducked
They might be AFK.
قد يكونون AFK.
We'll circle back to them.
سنعود إليهم لاحقًا.
Next is devinreal
التالي هو devinreal
Hi, I'm Devin.
مرحبًا، أنا Devin.
I make, uh Modpacks and stuff.
أصنع، أوه، Modpacks وأشياء أخرى.
One of you might use it.
قد يستخدمها أحدكم.
Great. Next is autumntxx.
رائع. التالي هو autumntxx.
Well, some people know me as Autumn, but I'm actually myself.
حسنًا، بعض الناس يعرفونني باسم Autumn، لكنني في الواقع أنا نفسي.
What do you do, Autumn?
ماذا تفعلين يا Autumn؟
I was born into a family of two kings,
ولدت في عائلة من ملكين،
Sadly, one became straight, and the other one was conquered.
للأسف، أحدهما أصبح مستقيمًا، والآخر تم غزوه.
From a young age I learned to fight for the kingdom.
منذ صغري تعلمت القتال من أجل المملكة.
Anywho, hope you all buy my bio novel
على أي حال، أتمنى أن تشتروا جميعًا روايتي السيرة الذاتية
now in stores near you!
متوفرة الآن في المتاجر القريبة منك!
Next up is VenomousSteam81.
التالي هو VenomousSteam81.
Hello, uh, I'm VSteam. Also known as Lizzie
مرحبًا، أنا VSteam. المعروفة أيضًا باسم Lizzie
I don't do much.
لا أفعل الكثير.
I have died
لقد مت
And went to this very wedding.
وذهبت إلى هذا العرس بالذات.
Amazing.
مدهش.
Thank you for your story, Lizzie.
شكرًا على قصتك، Lizzie.
Next up we have lmda22 (formerly known as jawa22).
التالي هو lmda22 (المعروف سابقًا باسم jawa22).
Ugh...
أوه...
I don't know what to say to be honest.
لا أعرف ماذا أقول بصراحة.
Let's try BaLLducked again.
لنجرب BaLLducked مرة أخرى.
[2G Interference]
[تداخل 2G]
Uh, my turn, I guess...
أوه، دوري، على ما أعتقد...
Hi, I'm Pixel.
مرحبًا، أنا Pixel.
I make mods.
أصنع تعديلات.
And music.
وموسيقى.
And texture art.
وفن نسيج.
And have tried painting.
وحاولت الرسم أيضًا.
And also sleep a lot.
وأنوم كثيرًا أيضًا.
And also do webdev.
وأعمل في تطوير الويب أيضًا.
I have essentially no verifiable facts about myself
ليس لدي أساسًا أي حقائق يمكن التحقق منها عن نفسي
other than “I go by WorldWidePixel”
باستثناء "أُعرف باسم WorldWidePixel"
And trust me, it's intentional.
وثق بي، هذا مقصود.
And that's me.
وهذا أنا.
So, to the ceremony!
الآن، إلى الحفل!
Hello all.
مرحبًا بالجميع.
We are here today to witness the holy amalgamation
نحن هنا اليوم لنشهد الاندماج المقدس
between Blurry and Pigu.
بين Blurry و Pigu.
Today is a special day
اليوم هو يوم خاص
Not only because people are in love
ليس فقط لأن الناس في حب
But also because this is the first marriage here in two years.
ولكن أيضًا لأن هذا هو أول زواج هنا منذ عامين.
I think this shows ROP can still be a place of love.
أعتقد أن هذا يظهر أن ROP لا يزال مكانًا للحب.
Except when it's not...
باستثناء عندما لا يكون...
Do not think of the war.
لا تفكر في الحرب.
without further adieu
بدون مزيد من اللغط
Can we welcome Piguman3 to the stage?
هل يمكننا الترحيب بـ Piguman3 على المسرح؟
This is pigu.
هذا هو pigu.
Say hi, Pigu.
قل مرحبًا، Pigu.
Hi.
مرحبًا.
-Hi Pigu
-مرحبًا Pigu
And now, the person we've all been waiting for.
والآن، الشخص الذي كنا ننتظره جميعًا.
Blurry!
Blurry!
Fashion by Northern Seamstresses.
الأزياء من تصميم Northern Seamstresses.
These two, are very love.
هذان الاثنان، حبهما كثير.
There am not word to describe how love much they am.
لا توجد كلمات لوصف مدى حبهم.
So thus, do we have the rings?
إذًا، هل لدينا الخواتم؟
Do we now have the rings?
هل لدينا الآن الخواتم؟
Let us exchange the rings.
لنتداول الخواتم.
I now pronounce you two...
أعلن الآن أنكما...
Married.
متزوجان.
You may kiss.
يمكنكما التقبيل.
Breaking News!
أخبار عاجلة!
woah, my voice seems to be normal again??
واو، يبدو أن صوتي طبيعي مرة أخرى؟؟
Weird structures have suddenly appeared in CRSS 3 !
ظهرت فجأة هياكل غريبة في CRSS 3!
Some structures, such as a glass house,
بعض الهياكل، مثل بيت زجاجي،
a wooden house,
وبيت خشبي،
and a mountain house have suddenly appeared around the spawn area.
وبيت جبلي ظهرت فجأة حول منطقة التكاثر.
No one is sure how these got here, but some conspiracy theorists say
لا أحد متأكد من كيفية وصولها إلى هنا، لكن بعض منظري المؤامرة يقولون
they're structures from a lost “CRSS2” world.
إنها هياكل من عالم "CRSS2" مفقود.
Of course, we all know there's CRSS 1 and CRSS 3, and there's no logical
بالطبع، كلنا نعرف أن هناك CRSS 1 و CRSS 3، وليس هناك تفسير منطقي
explanation to have some other one between these.
لوجود آخر بينهما.
Digital Landlord Workstation software maker
صانع برنامج Digital Landlord Workstation
“LandBab”, has announced a few days ago that they'll not only be
“LandBab”، أعلن قبل بضعة أيام أنهم لن يكتفوا
discontinuing their “WakeCalk” software,
بإيقاف برنامجهم “WakeCalk”،
but also take any land managed with the software to themselves.
ولكن سيأخذون أي أرض تمت إدارتها بالبرنامج لأنفسهم.
People are mad, but we ask that you all stay calm
الناس غاضبون، لكننا نطلب منكم جميعًا أن تظلوا هادئين
and do as they tell you. It would be unethical to tell you that you can
وتفعلوا ما يطلبونه منكم. سيكون من غير الأخلاقي أن نقول لكم إنه يمكنكم
migrate your workflow to Disableton and maintain ownership of your land, so we won't!
ترحيل سير عملكم إلى Disableton والحفاظ على ملكية أرضكم، لذا لن نفعل ذلك!
We're thrilled to announce that CRSS 3 inhabitants
نحن مسرورون بالإعلان عن أن سكان CRSS 3
are working on a transport system to take you around the worlds.
يعملون على نظام نقل ليأخذكم حول العوالم.
Not only that, it will be using the GREAT System for Route Information
ليس هذا فقط، بل سيستخدم نظام GREAT للحصول على معلومات المسار
available online and for semi automatic fee processing.
المتاحة عبر الإنترنت ولتجهيز رسوم شبه تلقائي.
The latter will only be available in CRSS 1.
هذا الأخير سيكون متاحًا فقط في CRSS 1.
It will use trains and train stations, and will take you to many
سيستخدم القطارات ومحطات القطار، وسيأخذكم إلى العديد
districts around the spawn area, as well as farther nations and cities as
من المناطق حول منطقة التكاثر، وكذلك الدول والمدن البعيدة
those begin to form.
عندما تبدأ في التكون.
Thanks for watching this edition of Quartz News Network!
شكرًا لمشاهدة هذه النسخة من Quartz News Network!
We really hope you enjoyed it. See you next month!
نأمل حقًا أن تكون قد استمتعت بها. نراكم الشهر المقبل!
Captions by Blurryface
ترجمة النصوص من قبل wha1es
Actual QNN #6 Post-credits Scene
مشهد ما بعد النهاية الفعلي لـ QNN #6